scottrade.com 2015-02-04

# Privacy Statement

                                             Privacy Statement
FACTS         WHAT DOES SCOTTRADE DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
              Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
              consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how
Why?          we collect, share and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
              understand what we do.
              The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have
              with us. This information can include:
What?            • Social Security number and Employment information
                 • Account balances and transaction history
                 • Credit history and Investment experience
              All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
              business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
How?          customers’ personal information; the reasons Scottrade chooses to share; and whether you can
              limit this sharing.
                                                                                     Does
                                                                                                 Can you limit
Reasons we can share your personal information                                   Scottrade
                                                                                                 this sharing?
                                                                                    share?
For our everyday business purposes –
                        such as to process your transactions, maintain your
                                                                                      Yes                 No
                        account(s), respond to court orders and legal
                        investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you                Yes                 No
For joint marketing with other financial companies                                    Yes                 No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
                                                                                      Yes                 No
                        information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
                                                                                      Yes                Yes
                        information about your creditworthiness
For our affiliates to market to you                                                   Yes                Yes
For non-affiliates to market to you                                                   No         We don’t share
                      Call (800) 619-7283 – our menu will prompt you through your choices.
                      Please note: If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days
To limit
                      from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to
our sharing           share your information as described in this notice.
                      However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?            Call 1-800-619-7283 or go to www.scottrade.com.
Who we are
Who is providing                     Scottrade, Inc.; Scottrade Bank, FSB; Boulevard Bank;
this notice?                         Scottrade Investment Management, Inc.
       Rev. August 2014                                Member FINRA/SIPC                          Page 1 of 3

 What we do
                                        To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we
 How does Scottrade protect
                                        use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include
 my personal information?
                                        computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
                                        We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
                                           • Open an account or perform transactions
 How does Scottrade collect                • Give us your contact information or make a wire transfer
 my personal information?                  • Make deposits or withdrawals from your account
                                        We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                        bureaus, affiliates or other companies.
                                        Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
                                           • Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about
                                             your creditworthiness
 Why can’t I limit all sharing?            • Affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                           • Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
                                         State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit
                                         sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
 What happens when I limit
 sharing for an account I hold          Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
 jointly with someone else?
 Definitions
                                        Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial
 Affiliates                             and nonfinancial companies.
                                        Our affiliates include Boulevard Bank and companies with a Scottrade name.
                                        Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
 Nonaffiliates                          financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                        Scottrade does not share with non-affiliates so they can market to you.
                                        A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together
                                        market financial products or services to you.
 Joint marketing
                                        Our joint marketing partners include mortgage lenders, credit card companies
                                        and other financial service providers.
 Other important information
We will continue to share information to the extent permissible by law. We may further limit information sharing to comply
with more restrictive state laws:
    • For accounts with a Vermont mailing address – we do not share information about your creditworthiness with any
       of our affiliates without your consent; however, we may share information about transactions and experiences with
       you without your consent.
    • For accounts with a California mailing address – The following page contains an additional notice describing
       the privacy choices available under California law.
Scottrade, Inc. and Scottrade Bank are separate but affiliated companies and are wholly-owned
subsidiaries of Scottrade Financial Services, Inc. Brokerage products                    and services offered by
Scottrade, Inc. – Member FINRA and SIPC. Deposit products and services offered by Scottrade Bank,
Member FDIC.
         Rev. August 2014                                Member FINRA/SIPC                                Page 2 of 3

                                        California Privacy Notice
                                  Important Privacy Choices for California Residents
   You have the right to control whether we share some of your personal information. Please read the
                       following information carefully before you make your choices below.
Your Rights
 You have the following rights to restrict the sharing of personal and financial information with our affiliates
 (companies we own or control) and outside companies with whom we do business. Nothing in this form prohibits
 the sharing of information necessary for us to follow the law, as permitted by law, or to give you the best service
 on your accounts with us. This includes sending you information about some other products or services.
Your Choices
 Restrict Information Sharing With Affiliates: Unless you instruct us otherwise, we may share personal and
 financial information about you with companies we own or control.
 Restrict Information Sharing With Outside Companies: Unless you instruct us otherwise, we may share
 personal and financial information about you with outside companies with whom we do business to provide
 financial products and services.
Time-Sensitive Reply
 You may make your privacy choices at any time; however, if we do not hear from you we may share some of
 your information with affiliated companies and outside companies as described above.
To exercise your choices, do one of the following:
 1. Complete the form below, then *mail to: Scottrade, Inc.
                                                  Attn. Privacy Department
                                                  P.O. Box 31759
                                                  St. Louis MO
                                                  63131-0759
       *email CAprivacy@scottrade.com to request a postage-paid return envelope
  2. Complete the form below, then fax to (855) 339-5128 Attn. Privacy Department.
---------------------------------------------------------------
          Scottrade Information Privacy Request – California Residents ONLY
                            The choice(s) indicated below will remain unless you state otherwise.
(_) Don’t share my personal & financial information with your affiliated companies.
(_) Don’t share my personal & financial information with outside companies with whom you do business.
Accountholder Name:
Account Number:                               Email (if applicable):
Signature:                                                                               Date:
        Rev. August 2014                                Member FINRA/SIPC                            Page 3 of 3
